<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Monkey Liberty</string>
    <string name="ap_author">© Monkey Liberty</string>
    <string name="image_chooser">Pick Your Image</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="gtggtgt">the actual execution of the estimate by the Ministry of Defense of Ukraine, in terms of months, differs significantly from the approved allocation plan for the corresponding year, namely: the largest share of expenditures (more than 30% of the amount of annual allocations) is carried out in the last months of the year: November and December.\nMulti-criteria analysis methods are suitable for solving a large number of real problems of a different nature. \nSome of the most popular methods used for troubleshooting multi attribute decision making include the analytic hierarchy process (AHP) method, ELECTRE method, PROMETHEE method, TOPSIS method, the simple additive weighting (SAW) and many others.\nknown as Technique for Order of Preference by Similarity to Ideal Solution, is a multi-criteria decision analysis method. It compares a set of alternatives based on a pre-specified criterion. The method is used in the business across various industries, every time we need to make an analytical decision based on collected data.During planning the state budget of Ukraine the historical principle is mainly used, planning of resources is carried out on the basis of the already distributed volume.</string>
    <string name="gtgtgt">During planning the state budget of Ukraine the historical principle is mainly used, planning of resources is carried out on the basis of the already distributed volume. At the same time, at the end of the budget period, the evaluation use of funds is carried out ex post facto and does not affect the already approved annual budget. When planning and evaluating the level of efficiency of the use of funds, it is important to give weight to each of the criteria that must be taken into account. The list of such criteria is quite large and diverse. The use of multi-criteria analysis methods is the best way to optimize such activities. Such methods as AHP, ELECTRE, PROMETHEE, TOPSIS, SAW is used in the business across various industries, every time we need to make an analytical decision based on collected data. The application of such multi-criteria scoring methods will ensure an increase in the level of effectiveness of management decision-making in the field of planning the states defense budget. Multi-criteria decision making refers to the determination of the best alternative in the conditions where there is a larger number of, usually, mutually conflicting criteria. The real problems have some common characteristics, namely: - a large number of criteria; conflict among the criteria; not comparable units of measurement</string>
</resources>